http://www.usacracing.com/index.php/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.
SECURITY POLICY
Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.
REFUND POLICY
Any request for refund will be provided as a credit to the credit card used at the time of purchase, but only within five (5) business days of original transaction.
About Your Privacy
The United States Auto Club takes online privacy very seriously. Simply stated, we will not distribute information about you, such as your name, mailing address, phone number and other personal information to anyone other than an affiliated third party. Affiliated third parties are companies that sponsor the United States Auto Club. The United States Auto Club reserves the right to alter its privacy principles, as business needs require. Visitors from outside the United States should be aware that any personal information they provide will be stored in the United States in accordance with U.S. law.
While visiting this Web site, information about your visit may be collected and stored for analytical purposes. There are also several opportunities on this Web site for you to provide information about you and your interests. If you provide personal information to assist the United States Auto Club in responding to your request, this information will be stored to enable follow-up communications. It may be used for marketing research and other marketing purposes, and may be shared with affiliated third parties.
We may also store information about you on your computer in the form of a “cookie.” A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored within your browser when you visit a cookie-enabled Web site. Cookies are often used to provide you with a more personal experience when you visit websites such as USAC Racing. As you browse the Web, cookie-enabled sites may send cookies to your browser. Your browser may let you control whether the browser accepts cookies, rejects cookies, or notifies you when a cookie is sent to you. You may find more information on “cookies” on other, non United States Auto Club Web sites.
Copyrights
Copyright 2008 United States Auto Club. All Rights Reserved. The text, images, graphics, sound files, animation files, video files and their arrangement on this Web site are all subject to copyright and other intellectual property protection. These objects may not be copied for commercial use or distribution, nor may these objects be modified or reposted to other sites. This Web site may also contain images that are subject to the copyright rights of their providers. No license to the United States Auto Club intellectual property has been granted by this Internet site.
Trademarks
Unless otherwise indicated, all marks displayed on the United States Auto Club Internet sites are subject to the trademark rights of the United States Auto Club.
back to top
Contacts
USAC Racing
©
2020
Privacy Policy
Scroll to Top
User Login
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
Create an account
